<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Let&#39;s play with Linux</title>
    <link>https://lpwlinux.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Let&#39;s play with Linux</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 12:59:08 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lpwlinux.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://lpwlinux.github.io/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 12:59:08 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lpwlinux.github.io/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello world! The first necessary post in a tech blog! My name is Konstantinos, I&amp;rsquo;m a junior-ish system administrator, currently working in a devops role. My pursuit is to get a better understanding of Linux, networking, all the apps that are used in the space that make our lives easier plus everything else that seems interesting to me!
The idea behind this blog (subject to change though) is to have posts of varying difficulty, ranging from easy and everyday stuff, basic operations to make our life simpler, to medium where we will delve in setting up applications and harder to bring multiple systems together with technologies such as containers etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the filesystem and manipulating files</title>
      <link>https://lpwlinux.github.io/posts/navigation-and-file-manipulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lpwlinux.github.io/posts/navigation-and-file-manipulation/</guid>
      <description>In the second post of the blog post we will discuss ways to navigate inside the filesystem, finding the files we are looking for and manipulating the text inside them.
Navigation First of all, let&amp;rsquo;s start with &amp;ldquo;navigation&amp;rdquo;. Quotes in place because I am taking for granted you know how to cd into a directory and thus labeling navigation the way to find what you are looking for and then getting to it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
